

TECHNICAL GAME
DESIGNER / QA TESTER

Contact

kevin031995@gmail.com

Links

LinkedIn

Portfolio

Itch.io Page

Featured Projects

Sacred Tails (PC-Win)
Long Delivery (PC-Win)

Skills

Game Design

Active Communication

Unity 3D (Advanced)

Godot Engine (Intermediate)

Unreal Engine 5 (Basic)

Pixel Art

2D animation

Manual Testing

Automated Web Testing

Languages

English: Advanced

Spanish: Native

Favorite Games

Dark souls, Bloodborne, Risk of Rain 2, Genshin Impact.

Profile Summary

Experienced Game Developer and Quality Assurance Tester with over 7 years of experience in game and software development, including commercial and hobbyist projects for mobile and PC platforms.

I have worked prototyping and designing games in a variety of genres including RPG, fighting, puzzle, and narrative adventure. Using different technologies including mobile, and web. Within different teams and teammates with unique backgrounds like 2d art, 3d art, programming, and UI design. I have also worked planning and executing test plans, managing teammates on the execution of test cases for websites used by hundreds of thousands of people.

Employment History

Unity 3D Programmer/2D animator at Xiara Studios, Remote

MARCH 2016 — JANUARY 2018

- Programming Gameplay and Multiplayer Features for 2D Fighting game for Android Platforms.
- Integration of 2D assets with code.
- Creation of 2D animations for playable characters.

Game Designer and Developer Freelance, Remote

JANUARY 2018 — PRESENT

- Design games on different genres (puzzle, platforms, narrative)
- Prototyping game concepts using Unity3D.and Unreal Engine 5
- Create 2D assets for prototypes (Characters, Environments, Animations)
- · Build and publish on windows platforms.

Principal Game Designer at Timba Games, Remote

APRIL 2022 — NOVEMBER 2022

- Design and balance Combat Statistics for more than 3000 playable units for a turn based game inspired by Pokemon.
- Authoring Game Design Documents and Game Flow diagrams.
- · Design and balance a deep PvP turn based Combat
- · Write NPC Dialogs.

QA automation at Jalasoft, Hybrid

NOVEMBER 2018 — AUGUST 2020

- Write and execute manual and automated tests for top software related to airlines revenue forecast.
- Deploy and configuration of test environments using Linux and Docker.
- Write and execute automation tests using Javascript, Ruby, and Python frameworks, and tools like Postman, SQL, and Excel.

Staff Advanced QA automation at Oktana, Remote

SEPTEMBER 2020 — MARCH 2022

- Planning and execution of regression testing of product releases every 2 weeks for a Salesforce web portal used by hundreds of developers.
- Ownership of product features on QA side.
- Write and execute manual tests for Salesforce products.

Education

Quality Automation Training Program, Foundation JALA, Cochabamba

JANUARY 2018 — SEPTEMBER 2018